Hello everyone!
This is Niyarikonjai!
In my previous video, I did a business etiquette challenge for answering the phone.
This time it's the email version!
Yay!
Okay, I'm going to give you all an email with a subject.
I'm going to give you an email on the subject, and you are going to reply to that email.
We will test whether you can reply to the e-mail without embarrassing yourself as a member of society!
Yes!
And this time, we have invited a manner instructor, Ms. Matsubara, to join us.
Please give her my best regards!
Thank you very much for your cooperation!
Yes, thank you again!
Email manners are essential for working people.
Let's learn it from there!
Yes, sir! Thank you very much for your cooperation!
I have prepared two themes for you this time as well.
The first is a reply to a wedding report from a business partner.
Oh!
That sounds like a good idea!
And the second is a refusal since appearing on the program
There are two types!
So let's decide who's going to take on which one!
Well, we'll celebrate the wedding of one of our clients.
Then we'll refuse to appear on the show!
Let's go for it!
We will read out the emails on the subject!
We will read out the emails from the marriage report!
Prefecture Name: Contact for three preferences due to marriage
Ikonoi Actress Planning Co.
Near Joy Corporation
Thank you very much for all your help!
My name is Aohei from Ikonoy Actress Planning Co.
I am very sorry for my personal matter.
Sorry?
I'm sorry for the trouble I caused earlier.
I'm going to make a cut.
I'm going to cut it.
I'm terribly sorry to make this personal, but I've just gotten married... and my name is Akahira.
I'm forced to contact you
With the change of orders, I've also changed my e-mail address.
I'm sorry to trouble you, but I would appreciate it if you would change it.
I'm sorry to trouble you, but we'd appreciate it if you'd change your e-mail address.
We will continue to work with the applicant.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
Akahira, Kyusei, Aohira
Oh!
How romantic!
Congratulations!
So this is how it comes. A wedding report.
It's the first I've heard of it.
Ai, will you present the "Request to Appear" segment?
Yes, please.
Request to appear in a program in your prefecture
Mr. Marumaru, Near Joy Corporation
We always play against each other.
Han
I get nervous, don't worry.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
We have been contacted by our head office group, Near Nicole Joy, to request an application to appear on our show.
We have been contacted by you to ask that you take a look at the details of the project we have in mind.
We would appreciate it if you could change the conditions of the schedule.
Near Broadcasting Station Near Joy Broadcasting Corporation Program name Near Joy Deserted Island Survival: 90 Days of Upheaval
Broadcasting period July to September 1, 2023
It's quite long.
I don't want to visit it.
DescriptionSurvival on a deserted island with bears and snakes, just the Nia Joy members, for 90 days.
There will be no staff either.
Please do your best to live together.
Surprise Mark Surprise Mark Surprise Mark Surprise Mark
Amazing!
Surprise mark is bad!
April to June, 2023 Content Wishers Nia Joy All Members
Nia Joy Broadcasting Corporation Nia Joy Broadcasting Corporation Inc. Inc. not to go out Planning Aohei
It's difficult
Sounds difficult.
Well then, this time we all want to write at once!
I'll do my best
I'd like to write all of you at once
Can I ask you to tell your customers that they should have water that is always available in your store?
I'm sorry, I've been waiting for your mail.
I wonder...? Is it?
I think I have two of them.
I should have two of them.
Let's go through the emails you wrote with your teacher.
Let's start with Ayumi.
Ayumi, it's a marriage report e-mail.
Here it is.
Oh, wow...
It's rather short.
You have to take care of it.
It's easy to get caught.
It's definitely organized.
It's very simple, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's very important that emails are written in a concise manner.
So I think we've done that.
The first thing you can do is, is there an address?
It would be nice if you could start with the name of the person to whom you are addressing the letter.
There's a greeting, a name.Greetings and names are available.
of congratulations on your marriage for this.
There were congratulations
There was also a mailer bracelet wedding press materials
Also, there's a note about the container.
Ah, but the answer... in another minute or so...
I'd like to say hello.
No more.
It would be nice if it contains a request, etc.
Will you be happy?
You can write "I'm so happy for you...
It's not bad.
But a blank is a blank.
We're friends after all.
I've written proof of your love.
That's great.
I have written proof of your love.
Just a few words
Just a word or two
Proof of your love
I'm sure your feelings will be conveyed.
Next time
And, yes, let's go to the verification.
Yes, I forgot.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much.
What a hassle. I like the wild feeling.
That's very Aimee-esque.
I did the emoji.
Then Aimi, please.
Aimi.
Let's start with Athena.
I wrote "Athena" and there was a part where I said hello.
I can write "Thank you very much".
Congratulations on your phone call!
I'm also giving you a little tadpole.
Thank you for calling us
This is also a very nice group of Aimi.
It's a very nice group.
I'm so glad to hear that you are changing from Ann to Akali.
Atremi lion.
I thought it would be a little too plain if we just had apparets.
I'm so glad!
Unique!
If you don't mind me saying this, it might be one thing.
It's a bit long for one word,
I'm not sure if it's too long, so I'm going to say, for a PC email,
About 35 characters or less,
If you close your answer, it will be easier to read.
The e-mail will appear on the screen like this,
Please try to make it more readable.
It would be even better if you could make it easier to read when you see it on the screen.
It would be even better if you give us your answer in a way that is easy to read when seen on the screen.
I'm sure that's a good idea.
You mean you're going to give us a reminder?
It's a small process.
a small stream of thoughts about a few things, such as a bath or a bathhouse
Kaori-yana (fragrance)
I'll accept something.
We're going to give them to you as a gift.
It's a present event!
dee
I don't have it.
ana
I would like to start with the group that is going to refuse the program.
I'm going to start with the group of people who are going to refuse the program, which is very difficult to refuse.
As I said about the program's appearance...
You have written it down well, haven't you?
You have written the pennator.
Athena.
And you also did a good job with the greetings and remnants for the other party.
You convey the feeling of "I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
In terms of the use of acceptance, a better one would be "I'm sorry, but...",
I dare you.
It's like "I'm sorry," or "I'm sorry, but....
I think that kind of wording is also acceptable.
Also, it would be better to improve it, so I'll just leave it here.
Well, thank you very much.
That's what I mean.
I will be next door.
I'm really sorry about the scheduling conflict.
It might come across softer if you say something like, "I'm so sorry.
I am sure that you have conveyed the feeling that we would be happy to hear from you again,
Since Matsubun has been written and a written document has appeared.
As for this composition, I am able to do it by myself.
Also, if you open a business, it will be done right.
That's the point.
It's all in order.
Lastly, I would like to start with Momo.
Please start with the thighs.
Yes, that's right.
You have written well from the premise.
There is also the part about writing about ordinary cases.
So this is also a part of it.
Oh, you guessed it.
Antenna, maybe.
You had an antenna in the content of the e-mail that came in.
Basically, the company name and
If it's the second e-mail, please write your full name.
If there is a pattern, etc., please write it down and we'll get back to you.You wrote to me that you have a pattern, etc.
Thanks for getting back to me.
Good, this is a good way to get out, and I'm sure it's well communicated in the requirements.
I would like to participate.
But it is difficult. I'd like to forego it.
I like the way you put it this way.
How did the first person know the words well?
Yes, I did.
Wow, I'm sorry. You know the language very well.
I think it is well balanced and well worded and so on.
Thank you very much.
It's wonderful.
That's great.
Now that you have been graded by the professor, I would like to start with the third-place winner,
I would like to start with the third-place winner.
Please start with the third-place winner.
Yes, I would like to start with the third-place winner. Okay, I will start with the third-place winner.
Third place, 7 points, please.
Huh? That's great.
Seven points?
That's amazing.
Wow, that's great.
I got a 7.5 on that phone call.
I was a lucky seven.
Oh, I see.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you very much.
She was a 7 earlier, too.
Yes. Continue,
Second place,
Murakami-san, with 8 points.
He scored 8 points earlier, too.
What?
Murakami-san scored 8 points.
That's great.
Next.
First place.
Yamada-san, with 9 points.
Ehh...
Thank you very much.
It's bub time.
It was well done.
Fourth place,
Six points, Ichiyo.
It was 6 points.
Because I got 3 points earlier.
That's double what you got earlier.
Double.
I think you all did well overall.
Glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug. Glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug, glug.
I thought I'd keep going.
You know what?
I think I was number one.
Oh! I'm so happy!
At least it was a makeup that everyone could feel from underneath!
Thank you very much!
Yes, so...
The queen of email etiquette is
Momoka!
Thank you very much!
Everyone, please leave the emails to me from now on!
Oh!
If you like this video
If you like this video, please click the Good button, comment, and subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Please do!
That's all!
I'm Queen Meow Meow Call!
Bye bye!